A Guide to the Records of the Policy Office of Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002-2006
Library of Virginia
- II. Regulations, 2002-2006 (accession 42413)., Extent: 12.25 cubic feet (34 boxes). (Box 4-37)
  - HEALTH AND HUMAN RESOURCES, Secretary of
    - Department of Social Services
      - Personnel Policies for Local Departments, 22 VAC 40-675, 552/1700 (part one) (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Personnel Policies for Local Departments, 22 VAC 40-675, 552/1700 (part two) (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Agency Placement Adoptions, AREVA, 22 VAC 40-250, 1041/1709 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Agency Placement Adoptions, Subsidy, 22 VAC 40-260, 1040/1708 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Child Protective Services, Implementing Differential Response, 22 VAC 40-705, 673/1664 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Licensed Adult Care Residences, 22 VAC 40-71, 554/1648 (part one) (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Licensed Adult Care Residences, 22 VAC 40-71, 554/1648 (part two) (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Child Protective Services, Central Registry Information, 22 VAC 40-700, 419/1640 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Minimum Standards for Licensed Family Day Homes, 22 VAC 40-110, 432/1553 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Minimum Standards for Licensed Family Day Systems, 22 VAC 40-121, 484/1554 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Economic and Employment Improvement Program for Disadvantaged Persons, 22 VAC 40-375, 1012/1608 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Investigation of Child Abuse and Neglect in Out-of-Family Complaints, 22 VAC 40-730, 672/1459 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Repeal of Agency Placement Adoptions, Guiding Principles, 22 VAC 40-220, 1013/1609 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Child Protective Services Release of Information to Family Advocacy Representatives of the United States Armed Forces, 22 VAC 40-720, 460/1639 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Child Day-Care Council, Public Participation Guidelines, 22 VAC 15-10, 85/1669 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Virginia Energy Assistance Program, 22 VAC 40-680, 974/1563 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Child Support Enforcement Program, 22 VAC 40-880, 407/1658 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - NATURAL RESOURCES, Secretary of
    - Department of Conservation and Recreation
      - Nutrient Management Training and Certification, 4 VAC 5-15, 1445/3460 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Department of Environmental Quality
      - SAPCB, Permits for Stationary Sources, Permits for New and Modified Sources (Rev. K04), 9 VAC 5-80, 1635/2951 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - SAPCB, Existing Stationary Sources, Consumer Products (Rev. G03), 9 VAC 5-40, 1261/2555 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - SAPCB, General Provisions, VOC Early Reduction Credit (Rev. C03), 9 VAC 5-20, 40, 1184/2571 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - SAPCB, Control of Motor Vehicle Emissions in the Northern Virginia Area (Remote Sensing Rev. MJ and MK), 9 VAC 5-91, 1260/2436 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - SAPCB, Emissions Trading, NOx Budget Trading Program Set-Aside Auctions (Rev. F02), 9 VAC 5-140, 1155/2520 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - SAPCB, Emissions Trading, NOx Budget Trading Program Flow Control (Rev. H02), 9 VAC 5-140, 1183/2031 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - SAPCB, Emissions Trading, NOx Budget Trading Program Set-Aside Auctions (Rev. F02), 9 VAC 5-140, 1155/1941 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - SAPCB, Hampton Roads VOC Emissions Control Area (Rev. G02), 9 VAC 5-20, 1160/1964 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - SAPCB, Existing Stationary Sources, Commercial/Industrial Solid Waste Incinerators (Rev. J00), 9 VAC 5-40-8200, 757/1463 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - SAPCB, Existing Stationary Sources, Small Municipal Waste Combustors (Rev. K00), 9 VAC 5-40-6550, 758/1464 (part one) (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - SAPCB, Existing Stationary Sources, Small Municipal Waste Combustors (Rev. K00), 9 VAC 5-40-6550, 758/1464 (part two) (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - SAPCB, On-Road Heavy-Duty Diesel Engines (Rev. A02), 9 VAC 5-230, 1014/1612 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - SAPCB, Existing Stationary Sources, Municipal Solid Waste Land-Fills (Rev. B02), 9 VAC 5-40-5800, 1050/1729 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - SAPCB, Existing Stationary Sources, VOC Emission Standards (Rev. C02), 9 VAC 5-40, 1049/1728 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - VWMB, Fees for permits and certificates, etc. (part one) (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - VWMB, Fees for permits and certificates, etc. (part two) (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - VWMB, Solid Waste Management, Waste Pile Permit by Rule, Amendment 4, 9 VAC 20-80, 1359/2729 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - VWMB, Transportation of Hazardous Materials, 9 VAC 20-110, 866/1741 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - VWMB, Solid Waste Management, Amendment 3, 9 VAC 20-80, 674/1770 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - SWCB, Virginia Pollution Abatement (VPA) Permit, Conform the Regulation to Federal Regulation, Amendments concerning CAFOS, 9 VAC 25-31, 1649/2997 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - SWCB, Solid Waste Management, Elimination of Radio Advertisement, Amendment 4a, 9 VAC 20-80, 1745/3163 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - SWCB, Water Quality Standards, Protect Designated Uses from the Impacts on Nutrients and Suspended Sediments in the Chesapeake Bay and its Tidal Tributaries, 9 VAC 25-260, 1368/2437, 1368/2760 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - SWCB, Water Quality Standards, Designation of Portions of the Cowpasture River and Simpson Creek as an Exceptional State Water, 9 VAC 25-260, 1579/2851 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - SWCB, Water Quality Standards, Designation of a Section of Little Stony Creek as an Exceptional Water, 9 VAC 25-260, 1248/2498 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - SWCB, Water Quality Standards, Designation of a Section of Ragged Island Creek as an Exceptional Water, 9 VAC 25-260, 1247/2566 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - SWCB, Water Quality Standards, Designation of a Section of Bottom Creek as an Exceptional Water, 9 VAC 25-260, 1246/2499 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - SWCB, Water Quality Standards, Designation of Lake Drummond and Portions of Six other Streams as Exceptional Waters, 9 VAC 25-260, 1245/2500 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - SWCB, Water Quality Standards, Designation of Several Waters in the Shenandoah National Park as Exceptional State Waters, 9 VAC 25-260, 1428/2578 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - SWCB, Petroleum Underground Storage Tank Financial Responsibility Requirements, 9 VAC 25-590, 1061/2374 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - SWCB, Nutrient Enriched Waters, Total Nitrogen and Phosphorus Limitations for Certain Permits with the Chesapeake Bay Watershed, 9 VAC 25-40, 1389/2490 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - SWCB, Water Quality Standards, Chesapeake Bay and Tidal Waters Criteria for Dissolved Oxygen, Water Clarity and Chlorophyll A and Designated Uses, 9 VAC 25-260, 1368/2437 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - SWCB, Water Quality Management Planning, Tennessee-Big Sandy River Basin, Section 90 B, 9 VAC 25-720, 1392/2494 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - SWCB, Water Quality Management Planning, Rappahannock River Basin, Section 70 B, 9 VAC 25-720, 1391/2492 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - SWCB, Water Quality Management Planning, New River Basin, Section 130 B, 9 VAC 25-720, 1390/2491 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - SWCB, Water Quality Management Planning, Potomac-Shenandoah Basin, Section 50 B, 9 VAC 25-720, 1395/2496 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - SWCB, Water Quality Management Planning, Roanoke River Basin, Section 80 B, 9 VAC 25-720, 1394/2495 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - SWCB, Local and Regional Water Supply Planning, 9 VAC 25-780, 1293/2296 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - SWCB, Water Quality Management Planning, Repeal, 9 VAC 25-720, etc. 624/2120 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - SWCB, Waste Treatment and Water Quality Management for the Dulles Area Watershed, 9 VAC 25-400, 1163/1978 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - SWCB, Wastewater Reclamation and Reuse, 9 VAC 25-740, 756/1981 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - SWCB, Fees for Permits and Certificates, 9 VAC 25-20, 1046/2011 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - SWCB, Financial Responsibility Requirements for Mitigation Associated with Tidal Dredging Projects, 9 VAC 25-770, 1161/1967 and 1979 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - SWCB, James River (Richmond Regional West) Surface Water Management Area, 9 VAC 25-760, 886/1875 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - SWCB, Discharge of Sewage and Other Wastes from Boats, 9 VAC 25-72, 73/1599 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - SWCB, Underground Storage Tanks: Technical Standards and Corrective Action Requirements, 9 VAC 25-580, 869/1506 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - SWCB, Water Quality Standards, Triennial Review Amendments, 9 VAC 25-260, 739/1595 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - SWCB, Facility and Aboveground Storage Tank (AST), 9 VAC 25-91, 966/1507 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Department of Game and Inland Fisheries
      - Watercraft: Motorboat Numbering, Fee Increase, 4 VAC 15-380, 1102/1835 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Department of Historic Resources
      - Historic Rehabilitation Tax Credits, 17 VAC 10-30, 858/1603 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - PUBLIC SAFETY, Secretary of
    - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control
      - Retail Operations, Sale of Soju by the Bottle, 3 VAC 5-50, 1562/2824 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Other Provisions, Direct Shipping Rules, 3 VAC 5-70, 1330/2452 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Requirements for Product Approval, Label Approval Revisions, 3 VAC 5-40, 1186/2034 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Tied-House Revisions, 3 VAC 5-30, 1185/2033 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Manufacturers and Wholesalers Operations/Business Entertainment and Gifts by Mixed Beverage Solicitors, 3 VAC 5-60, 825/1536 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Cider Peddling and Invoicing, 3 VAC 5-70, 826/1537 (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Advertising/Use of Athletics and Novelty and Specialty Items, 3 VAC 5-20, 822/1535 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - Tied-House/Customized Advertising Material, 3 VAC 5-30, 823/1534 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Retail Operations/Caterer Reports, 3 VAC 5-50, 841/1538 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Department of Corrections
      - Certification and Inspection of Local Jails, State Correctional Facilities, Residential Centers; Probation Offices under the authority of the Board of Corrections, 6 VAC 15-20, 1303/2309 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Department of Criminal Justice
      - Certification of Criminal Justice Instructors, 6 VAC 20-80, 1521/2761 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Compulsory In-Service Training Standards for Law-Enforcement Officers, Jailors or Custodial Officers, Courtroom Security Officers, Process Service, 6 VAC 20-30, 1522/2762 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Conservators of the Peace, 6 VAC 20-230, 1405/2513 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Crime Prevention Specialists, 6 VAC 20-180, 1301/2306 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Permitting DNA Analysis upon Arrest for All Violent Felonies and Certain Burglaries, 6 VAC 20-210, 1206/2077 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Private Security Services, 6 VAC 20-171, 1024/1659 (part one) (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Private Security Services, 6 VAC 20-171, 1024/1659 (part two) (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Department of Juvenile Justice
      - Public Participation Guidelines, 6 VAC 35-10, 1447/2633 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Juvenile Record Information and the Virginia Juvenile Justice Information System, 6 VAC 35-160, 885/1774 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Standards for Juvenile Residential Facilities, 6 VAC 35-140, 755/1769 (part one) (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Standards for Juvenile Residential Facilities, 6 VAC 35-140, 755/1769 (part two) (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Approving State Reimbursement of Local Juvenile Residential Facility Costs, 6 VAC 35-30, 753/1066 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Minimum Standards for Research Involving Human Subjects or Records of DJJ, 6 VAC 35-170, 1103/1836 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Minimum Standards for Virginia Delinquency Prevention and Youth Development Act Grant Programs, 6 VAC 35-60, 751/1881 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Standards for Nonresidential Services Available to Juvenile and Domestic Relations District Courts, 6 VAC 35-150, 750/1877 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Certification Process for Residential and Non-Residential Programs, 6 VAC 35-20, 393/1210 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - TRANSPORTATION, Secretary of
    - Department of Motor Vehicles
      - Commercial Driver Training School, Repeal Existing Commercial Driver Training School Regulations and Promulgate New Regulations pursuant to recent statutory changes, 24 VAC 20-120, 1541/2798 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Requirements for Proof of Residency to Obtain a Virginia Driver's License or Photo Identification Card, 24 VAC 20-70, 943/1970 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Regulatory Action (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Department of Transportation
      - Roadside Management Program, 24 VAC 30-121, 1515/2746 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Minimum Standards of Entrances to State Highways, 24 VAC 30-71, 924/1763 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Subdivision Street Requirements, 24 VAC 30-90, 91, 1234/2479 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- III. Legislative Files, 2002-2005 (accession 42414)., Extent: 47.95 cubic feet (137 boxes). (Box 38-174)
  The Legislative Files series is housed in 137 boxes and is arranged chronologically by legislative session. This series documents the Governor's Policy Office review of all legislation introduced by the General Assembly during the Warner administration. Each file usually contains the text of each bill including any amendments, bill tracking information, Governor's Summaries (prepared by the Division of Legislative Services), Legislative Action Summaries (for bills tabled, withdrawn or killed in committee), Governor's Policy Office Enrolled Bill Review Forms, Enrolled Bill Reviews (by Cabinet Secretary), Department of Planning and Budget Fiscal Impact Statements, Attorney General's Recommendations to the Governor and other miscellaneous legislation-related documents which explain in detail various bills brought before and voted upon by the General Assembly. In addition to providing the policy positions and decisions of the Warner administration, the Legislative Files may also be useful to researchers in determining legislative intent.
  Each Governor's Summary prepared by the Division of Legislative Services contains the bill number, patron, bill summary, other information and name of reviewer. The Enrolled Bill Reviews, prepared by the agency most affected by the legislation, summarize the bill and the number of votes for passage achieved by the House and Senate. The reviews include affected constituents' summary, agency analysis and recommendations, recommendations by the appropriate cabinet secretary and notations as to whether the Governor should sign, ask to amend or veto the bill. The Governor's Policy Office Enrolled Bill Review Form contains the vote in the House and Senate, a list and explanation of any no votes, fiscal impact (if any), summary of bill and comments by a Policy Office analyst (Ryan Childress, Suzette Denslow, Steven Gould, David Hallock, Anna Healy, Gail Jaspen, William L. Murray, Grant Neely or Wayne Turnage), and recommendations to Governor Warner from the Analyst, Director of Policy (Jane N. Kusiak, 2002 and Robert M. Blue, 2002-2005) and Chief of Staff (William H. Leighty) if the Governor should sign, veto or amend the bill. Some files contain Department of Planning and Budget fiscal impact statements which detail the monetary affect any legislation might have on the budget. The Office of the Attorney General's Recommendations to the Governor contain check boxes noting if the legislation conflicts with existing law or the Virginia and Federal constitutions, as well as any suggested amendments or comments. The Attorney General's Recommendations are restricted due to attorney-client privilege. Other files also contain correspondence including e-mail messages from bill supporters and opponents related to that particular bill. Also included in this series are Legislative Action Summaries that contain agency and cabinet secretary recommendations and handwritten comments and Governor's suggested amendments and veto messages.
  Notable legislation includes: Budget Bills, HB 30 (02), HB 29 (04), HB 30 (04) and HB 5001 (Special Session 2004); Educational Facility Bond Act of 2002, HB 99 (02) and SB 31 (02); creation of Virginia Information Technology Agency (VITA), HB 1926 (03) and SB 1247 (03); creation of the small, women, and minority-owned business (SWAM) program, HB 1145 (04) and SB 598 (04); the creation of the Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, SB 543 (04) and the Restructured Higher Education Financial and Administrative Operations Act, SB 1327 (05).
  - 2002 Session
    - House of Delegates
      - 2002 Session Statistics, Governor's Vetoes and Recommendations (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - 2002 Session Bills Approved by Governor or Enacted (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - 2002 Session Bills Passed House and Senate (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - HB 1 (02) Lottery; Transitional Provisions (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - HB 2 (02) Tennessee-Virginia Bi-State Thermal Authority (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - HB 3 (02) Experimental Family Courts (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - HB 4 (02) High-Occupancy Vehicle (HOV) Lanes (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - HB 5 (02) Participation in Virginia Independence Program; Exceptions (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - HB 6 (02) Motor Fuels Tax; Alternative Fuels Retailer Definition (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - HB 8 (02) Inspector General for MHMRSAS (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - HB 9 (02) Protection and Advocacy; Office for (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - HB 10 (02) Abolish Health Planning Board (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - HB 11 (02) Tuition Fees Charged In-State Undergraduate Students (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - HB 13 (02) Publication of Virginia State Bar Advisory Opinions (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - HB 15 (02) Solicitation of Contributions Act; Exemptions (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - HB 18 (02) Conservators of the Peace (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - HB 19 (02) Eastern Virginia Medical School; Name Change (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - HB 20 (02) Poor Debtor's Exemption; Funeral Expenses (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - HB 22 (02) High-Occupancy Vehicle (HOV) Lanes; Taxicabs (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - HB 23 (02) Sales and Use Tax Exemptions; Free Textbook Distribution to Professors (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - HB 24 (02) Charter; Town of Vienna (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - HB 26 (02) Retirement System; Employer Payment of Member Contributions (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - HB 27 (02) Claims; Kingdom Communications Group, LLC (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - HB 29 (02) Budget Bill; Amends Appropriation Act of 2000 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - HB 29 (02) Budget Bill; Amends Appropriation Act of 2000 (Box 38)
      - HB 29 (02) Budget Bill; Amends Appropriation Act of 2000 (Box 38)
      - HB 30 (02) Budget Bill; Appropriations for 2002-2004 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - HB 30 (02) Budget Bill; Appropriations for 2002-2004 (Box 39)
      - HB 35 (02) License Plates, Special; Abolishes Authorization for Various Groups (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - HB 36 (02) Constitutional Amendment; Property Tax Exemptions (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - HB 37 (02) Communications Between Physicians and Patients (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - HB 39 (02) Individual Income Tax; Refunds (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - HB 41 (02) Agencies Requesting Wiretaps (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - HB 44 (02) Pronouncement of Death (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - HB 46 (02) School Crisis and Emergency Management Plans (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - HB 49 (02) Soil and Water Conservation Districts; Boards of Directors and Terms (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - HB 50 (02) Workers' Comp.; Police Officers Metro. Wash. Airports Authority (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - HB 51 (02) Magistrates, Special; Deletes Obsolete References (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - HB 52 (02) Motor Vehicles; Deletes Obsolete References (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - HB 53 (02) Food Products, Miscellaneous; Deletes Obsolete References (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - HB 54 (02) Emplaning Service Fee; Deletes Obsolete References (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - HB 55 (02) Chancery Court of the City of Richmond; Deletes Obsolete References (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - HB 61 (02) Courthouses; Construction and Repair (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - HB 66 (02) Absentee Ballots; Replacement for Certain Disabled or Ill Voters (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - HB 67 (02) Charging a Violation of Driving While Intoxicated (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - HB 68 (02) Appeal by the Commonwealth (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - HB 71 (02) Retirement System; Deferred Compensation and Cash Match Plans (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - HB 72 (02) Limited Access to Safe-Deposit Box (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - HB 73 (02) Letter of Instruction or Memorandum into Will (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - HB 78 (02) Workers' Comp. Commission; Availability of Records to VRS (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - HB 79 (02) Duties of State Council of Higher Education (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - HB 80 (02) Retirement System; Payment of Life Insurance and Retirement Benefits (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - HB 81 (02) Remedy for Arbitrary Refusal of Motor Vehicle Insurance Claim (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - HB 82 (02) Motor Vehicle Registration Fees for Emergency Services (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - HB 85 (02) Roadside Memorials (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - HB 86 (02) Sales and Use Tax; Definition of Food (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - HB 89 (02) License Plates, Special; United We Stand (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - HB 90 (02) Policies Regarding Medication Recommendations by School Personnel (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - HB 91 (02) Water Protection Permit; Dredging Project Mitigation (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - HB 95 (02) Campus Police; Expansion of Jurisdiction (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - HB 97 (02) Limitations on Obligations of Borrowers (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - HB 98 (02) Payment of Small Account Balances (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - HB 99 (02) Educational Facilities Bond Act of 2002 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - HB 100 (02) Higher Educational Institutions Bond Act of 2002 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - HB 101 (02) Elections; Conditional Votes (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - HB 102 (02) VCU, School of Medicine, Inova Division (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - HB 106 (02) Posting of "In God We Trust" in Local Government Admin. Buildings (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - HB 107 (02) Posting of "In God We Trust" in Courtrooms (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - HB 108 (02) Posting of "In God We Trust" in All Schools (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - HB 115 (02) Golf Carts (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - HB 118 (02) Purchase of Handguns of Certain Officers (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - HB 119 (02) One Handgun a Month Purchase Limitation (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - HB 124 (02) Mandatory Provisions of Subdivision Ordinances (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - HB 127 (02) Minors' Consent to Treatment for Substance Abuse (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - HB 128 (02) Overweight Vehicles; Liquidated Damages (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - HB 137 (02) Confederate Cemeteries; Ettrick Cemetery (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - HB 140 (02) Insurance Fraud Within DSP; Abolishes Sunset Provision (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - HB 146 (02) Reporting Dangerous Microbes and Pathogens (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - HB 147 (02) Wilderness Road State Park (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - HB 148 (02) Solid Waste Landfills; Closure (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - HB 150 (02) New Home Breach of Warranty; Provisions (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - HB 151 (02) Additional Fees in Courts that Provide Legal Services for the Poor (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - HB 153 (02) Hemophilia Advisory Board; Composition (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - HB 154 (02) Health; Certain Unused Drugs Provided to Free Clinics (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - HB 159 (02) SOL; Website Suggestions for Improvements (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - HB 160 (02) Denial of Driver's License for Truancy (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - HB 163 (02) Delayed Local Elections Following Redistricting (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - HB 165 (02) Charter; City of Fairfax (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - HB 167 (02) Law-Enforcement Notices Sent Through Mail (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - HB 169 (02) Election Materials; Security and Retention Requirements (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - HB 173 (02) Freedom of Information Advisory Council (Box 40, Folder 6)